Summary

Hi! I'm Felipe Monteiro

— a music producer
and sound designer
with over 5 years of
study and practices in
the field.

My most recent project involved producing an EP from scratch as a service for another artist - composition, production, recording of vocals, mixing and mastering.

Currently based in São Paulo, Brazil.

Experience

ThayB

Single & EP production · October 2023 - Ongoing

- Composing and producing the instrumentals
- Vocal recording sessions
- Mixing & Mastering for streaming

yLLop - Personal Project

Singles, EP & LP - June 2021 - Ongoing

- Composing and producing the songs
- Synthesis of electronic elements
- Mixing & Mastering for streaming

Discos & Girafas

Podcast production · October 2020 - July 2022

- · Recording of the raw material
- Audio editing & FX
- Mixing & Mastering for streaming

Education

Anhembi Morumbi

Music Production January 2023 - December 2024

ETEC Getulio Vargas

High School & Technician January 2012 - December 2014

Details

Felipe de Carvalho **Monteiro**

Portfolio

yllopmusic.vercel.app

Email

yllopmusic@gmail.com felipe0597@hotmail.com

Phone

+55 11 96361 4921

Skills

Music / Audio

Music Theory · Sound Design · Synthesis · Mixing · Mastering · Sample Manipulation · Editing · FX Chain

Tools

FL Studio · Pro Tools · Xfer Serum · Figma · Premiere · After Effects

Languages

- Portuguese (native)
- English (advanced)
- Spanish (basic)
- · Japanese (basic)